Political Research Associates Records MS014
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Publications, 1908 -- 2011; MS014.001; 91.2 Linear Feet
  - NARAL Publications, MS014.001.046.00019; National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League (NARAL) Foundation (Box 46)
  - The NASSCO 3 fought for safe working conditions, 1981; MS014.001.046.00020; Committee to Defend Nassco Workers (Box 46)
  - National Affairs, 2009; MS014.001.046.00021 (Box 46)
  - The National Alliance, 1987 -- 1994; MS014.001.046.00022 (Box 46)
  - National Anti-Klan Network Newsletter, 1982 -- 1985; MS014.001.046.00023; National Anti-Clan Network (Box 46)
  - National Association of Pro-Life Nurses, MS014.001.046.00024 (Box 46)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy reports, 1997 -- 1999; MS014.001.046.00025; National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy (Box 46)
  - National Conservative Examiner, 1998; MS014.001.046.00026 (Box 46)
  - National Day of Prayer publications, 2002; MS014.001.046.00027; National Day of Prayer (Box 46)
  - National Defender, 1992 -- 2000; MS014.001.046.00028; National Defense Committee (Box 46)
  - NAC Precious Metals Advisory, 1981; MS014.001.047.00001; North American Coin and Currency (Box 47)
  - National Alliance: A House Divided, 2002; MS014.001.047.00002; Center for Democratic Renewal (Box 47)
  - The National Educator [1 of 7], 1982 -- 1994; MS014.001.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - The National Educator [2 of 7], 1986 -- 1987; MS014.001.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - The National Educator [3 of 7], 1985 -- 1994; MS014.001.047.00005 (Box 47)
  - The National Educator [4 of 7], 1981 -- 1982; MS014.001.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - The National Educator [5 of 7], 1983; MS014.001.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - The National Educator [6 of 7], 1985; MS014.001.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - The National Educator [7 of 7], 1983 -- 1985; MS014.001.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - National Enquirer, 2008; MS014.001.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - National Family Reporter, 1982 -- 1984; MS014.001.047.00011; United Families of America (Box 47)
  - National Fluoridation News, 1968 -- 1975; MS014.001.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - National Front News, MS014.001.047.00013; The National Directorate of the National Front (Box 47)
  - National Laymen's Digest, 1981 -- 1982; MS014.001.047.00014; The National Laymen's Council of the Church League of America (Box 47)
  - National Liberty Journal [1 of 6], 2001 -- 2002; MS014.001.047.00015; Jerry Fallwell (Box 47)
  - National Liberty Journal [2 of 6], 2000; MS014.001.047.00016; Jerry Fallwell (Box 47)
  - National Liberty Journal [3 of 6], 2000 -- 2002; MS014.001.047.00017; Jerry Fallwell (Box 47)
  - National Liberty Journal [4 of 6], 2003; MS014.001.047.00018; Jerry Fallwell (Box 47)
  - National Liberty Journal [5 of 6], 1999; MS014.001.047.00019; Jerry Fallwell (Box 47)
  - National Liberty Journal [6 of 6], 1999 -- 2004; MS014.001.047.00020; Jerry Fallwell (Box 47)
  - National Monitor of Education [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1997; MS014.001.047.00021 (Box 47)
  - National Monitor of Education [2 of 2], 1992 -- 1994; MS014.001.047.00022 (Box 47)
  - National News Reporter, 1998; MS014.001.047.00023; United Broadcasting Network (Box 47)
  - National Program Letter, 1990; MS014.001.047.00024; American Citizenship Center (Box 47)
  - National Reform Association News, MS014.001.047.00025; National Reform Association (Box 47)
  - The National Reporter, 1985 -- 1987; MS014.001.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - National Security Alert, MS014.001.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - National Security Report, 1994; MS014.001.048.00003; American Security Council and the American Security Council Foundation (Box 48)
  - National Socialist Observer, 1984 -- 1985; MS014.001.048.00004; National Socialist Liberation Front (Box 48)
  - National Student Education Fund Report, 1977 -- 1979; MS014.001.048.00005; National Student Education Fund (Box 48)
  - National Vanguard, 1979 -- 1992; MS014.001.048.00006; National Alliance (Box 48)
  - National Writers Union 1990 Directory/Handbook, MS014.001.048.00007; National Writers Union (Box 48)
  - Nationalism, Anti-Semitism, and the Anti-Globalization Movement, 2003; MS014.001.048.00008; De Fabel van de Illegaal (Box 48)
  - Nationalism Today, 1984 -- 1986; MS014.001.048.00009 (Box 48)
  - The Nationalist, 1986 -- 1991; MS014.001.048.00010 (Box 48)
  - The Nationalist Times [1 of 6], 2005 -- 2006; MS014.001.048.00011; American Nationalist Union (Box 48)
  - The Nationalist Times [2 of 6], 2001 -- 2002; MS014.001.048.00012; American Nationalist Union (Box 48)
  - The Nationalist Times [3 of 6], 2002 -- 2003; MS014.001.048.00013; American Nationalist Union (Box 48)
  - The Nationalist Times [4 of 6], 2003 -- 2004; MS014.001.048.00014; American Nationalist Union (Box 48)
  - The Nationalist Times [5 of 6], MS014.001.048.00015; American Nationalist Union (Box 48)
  - The Nationalist Times [6 of 6], MS014.001.048.00016; American Nationalist Union (Box 48)
  - Native Canadian, 1985; MS014.001.048.00017; Native Canadian Media (Box 48)
  - Nazareth, 1991; MS014.001.048.00018; Nazareth Publishing (Box 48)
  - NCCWO Bulletin, 1982; MS014.001.048.00019; Nation Lawyer's Guild (Box 48)
  - NCFE Bulletin, 1993 -- 1998; MS014.001.048.00020; National Campaign for Freedom of Expression (Box 48)
  - NCMI News Report, 2010; MS014.001.048.00021; New Covenant Ministries International (Box 48)
  - NEA Reporter, 1981; MS014.001.048.00022 (Box 48)
  - Near the Cross: When Does Free Speech Become Hate Speech?, 2002; MS014.001.048.00023; Center for Democratic Renewal (Box 48)
  - Necessary Force, 1995 -- 1997; MS014.001.048.00024; The Missouri 51st Militia (Box 48)
  - The NED Backgrounder, 1992 -- 1993; MS014.001.048.00025; The Inter-Hemispheric Education Resource Center (Box 48)
  - Negative Population Growth, 1986 -- 2008; MS014.001.048.00026; Negative Population Growth, Inc. (Box 48)
  - NET On Screen, 1995; MS014.001.048.00027; NET-Political NewsTalk Network (Box 48)
  - Network News, 1996; MS014.001.048.00028; Christians Encouraging One Another (Box 48)
  - Network News, 1996 -- 2002; MS014.001.048.00029; National Network for Immigrant and Refugee Rights (Box 48)
  - Network News, 2000 -- 2008; MS014.001.048.00030; Texas Freedom Network (Box 48)
  - Network News Flash, 1997 -- 2003; MS014.001.048.00031; Montana Human Rights Network (Box 48)
  - The New Common Sense, 1994; MS014.001.049.00001; The Tucson Institute (Box 49)
  - New Democracy, 1997 -- 2001; MS014.001.049.00002 (Box 49)
  - New Democrat, 1999; MS014.001.049.00003; Democratic Leadership Council (Box 49)
  - New Dimensions [1 of 2], 1990 -- 1991; MS014.001.049.00004; New Dimensions (Box 49)
  - New Dimensions [2 of 2], MS014.001.049.00005; New Dimensions (Box 49)
  - The New Federalist [1 of 7], 1995 -- 2002; MS014.001.049.00006 (Box 49)
  - The New Federalist [2 of 7], 2000 -- 2002; MS014.001.049.00007 (Box 49)
  - The New Federalist [3 of 7], 2000; MS014.001.049.00008 (Box 49)
  - The New Federalist [4 of 7], 2000 -- 2001; MS014.001.049.00009 (Box 49)
  - The New Federalist [5 of 7], 2000 -- 2001; MS014.001.049.00010 (Box 49)
  - The New Federalist [6 of 7], 2001; MS014.001.049.00011 (Box 49)
  - The New Federalist [7 of 7], 1993 -- 2000; MS014.001.049.00012 (Box 49)
  - The New Hot Blast, 1993; MS014.001.049.00013; Liberating Learning (Box 49)
  - New Jewish Agenda, 1991; MS014.001.049.00014 (Box 49)
  - The New Letter, 1962; MS014.001.049.00015; Nationalist News Service (Box 49)
  - New Man [1 of 8], 1996 -- 2000; MS014.001.049.00016; Strang Communications (Box 49)
  - New Man [2 of 8], 1998 -- 2006; MS014.001.049.00017; Strang Communications (Box 49)
  - New Man [3 of 8], 1999 -- 2000; MS014.001.049.00018; Strang Communications (Box 49)
  - New Man [4 of 8], 2001 -- 2003; MS014.001.049.00019; Strang Communications (Box 49)
  - New Man [5 of 8], 2000 -- 2004; MS014.001.049.00020; Strang Communications (Box 49)
  - New Man [6 of 8], 2003 -- 2004; MS014.001.050.00001; Strang Communications (Box 50)
  - New Man [7 of 8], 2001 -- 2006; MS014.001.050.00002; Strang Communications (Box 50)
  - New Man [8 of 8], 2006 -- 2007; MS014.001.050.00003; Strang Communications (Box 50)
  - The New Media Report, 1997; MS014.001.050.00004; New Media News Corporation (Box 50)
  - New Nation, 1985; MS014.001.050.00005 (Box 50)
  - The New Order [1 of 2], 1978 -- 1994; MS014.001.050.00006; The New Order (Box 50)
  - The New Order [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1997; MS014.001.050.00007; The New Order (Box 50)
  - New Pages, 1988; MS014.001.050.00008; New Pages Press (Box 50)
  - The New Republican, 1991; MS014.001.050.00009 (Box 50)
  - The "New Right" Post-Election, 1981; MS014.001.050.00010; Engage/Social Action (Box 50)
  - New Right Report, 1977 -- 1982; MS014.001.050.00011; Viguerie Communications Corporation (Box 50)
  - The New Settler Interview, 1993; MS014.001.050.00012 (Box 50)
  - New Solidarity, 1984; MS014.001.050.00013; Campaigner Publications (Box 50)
  - New Voices, MS014.001.050.00014; National Center for Immigrant Students (Box 50)
  - New Voices, 2008; MS014.001.050.00015; Peace through Justice (Box 50)
  - The New York Guardian [1 of 2], 1993; MS014.001.050.00016 (Box 50)
  - The New York Guardian [2 of 2], 1993; MS014.001.050.00017 (Box 50)
  - New York Hangover, 2000; MS014.001.050.00018 (Box 50)
  - News & Views, 1967 -- 1982; MS014.001.050.00019; Church League of America (Box 50)
  - News and Views Digest, 1983 -- 1984; MS014.001.050.00020; Church League of America (Box 50)
  - News Flash, 1999 -- 2003; MS014.001.050.00021; Media Research (Box 50)
  - News from the Front, 2008 -- 2009; MS014.001.050.00022; David Horowitz Freedom Center (Box 50)
  - News from the Hill, 2008 -- 2009; MS014.001.050.00023; Virginia Theological Seminary (Box 50)
  - News from the Homefront, 1995; MS014.001.050.00024; Family Violence Prevention Fund (Box 50)
  - News from the Playboy Foundation, MS014.001.050.00025; Playboy Foundation (Box 50)
  - News from the Schlesinger Library, 2001; MS014.001.050.00026; The Arthur and Elizabeth Schlesinger Library (Box 50)
  - News from MCLI, 1989; MS014.001.050.00027; Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute (Box 50)
  - News Notes, 1992; MS014.001.050.00028; Boston Justice and Peace Center (Box 50)
  - News Notes, 2001; MS014.001.050.00029; Datacenter (Box 50)
  - News Telegraph, 1995; MS014.001.050.00030; Piasa Publishing Co. (Box 50)
  - News Watch, 1998; MS014.001.050.00031; Center for Integration and Improvement of Journalism at San Francisco State University (Box 50)
  - NewsMax [1 of 2], 2004; MS014.001.050.00032; Newsmax (Box 50)
  - NewsMax [2 of 2], 2002 -- 2004; MS014.001.050.00033; Newsmax (Box 50)
  - News/Views, 1993; MS014.001.050.00034; Atlanta Friends National Legislation Committee (Box 50)
  - Never to Live, Laugh or Love, 1980; MS014.001.050.00035; Catholics United for Life (Box 50)
  - NFD Newsletter, 1979; MS014.001.050.00036; National Federation for Decency (Box 50)
  - NFF Update, 1991; MS014.001.050.00037; National Forum Foundation (Box 50)
  - NGRA Newsletter, 1986 -- 1987; MS014.001.050.00038; National Gay Rights Advocates Newsletter (Box 50)
  - Nightlines Weekly, 1994; MS014.001.050.00039; Outlines (Box 50)
  - NNAF Newsletter, 2003 -- 2007; MS014.001.050.00040; National Network of Abortion Funds (Box 50)
  - The Noble Report, 1996; MS014.001.050.00041; Preamble Foundation (Box 50)
  - Noel News, 2006; MS014.001.050.00042; NOEL (Box 50)
  - NOLO News, 1989; MS014.001.050.00043; Nolo Press (Box 50)
  - North American Farmer, 1986; MS014.001.050.00044; North American Farm Alliance (Box 50)
  - North Carolina Republican Party, 1982; MS014.001.050.00045 (Box 50)
  - North Carolinians Against Racist and Religious Violence Newsletter, 1986 -- 1992; MS014.001.050.00046; North Carolinians Against Racist and Religious Violence (Box 50)
  - North Star Fund News, 2005; MS014.001.050.00047; North Star Fund (Box 50)
  - Northeast Action News, 2004; MS014.001.050.00048; Northeast Action (Box 50)
  - The Northern Forest Forum, 1992 -- 1993; MS014.001.050.00049 (Box 50)
  - Northern Landmark Missionary Baptist, 2006; MS014.001.051.00001 (Box 51)
  - Northern Sun News, 1988; MS014.001.051.00002; Northern Sun Alliance (Box 51)
  - Northwest Beacon, MS014.001.051.00003 (Box 51)
  - Northwest Ethnic News, 1990; MS014.001.051.00004; Ethnic Heritage Council (Box 51)
  - Northwest Orchestra, MS014.001.051.00005; Northwest Coalition Against Malicious Harassment (Box 51)
  - The Northwestern Review [1 of 3], 1982 -- 1984; MS014.001.051.00006; Northwestern University (Box 51)
  - The Northwestern Review [2 of 3], 1984 -- 1986; MS014.001.051.00007; Northwestern University (Box 51)
  - The Northwestern Review [3 of 3], 1986 -- 1987; MS014.001.051.00008; Northwestern University (Box 51)
  - Notable Quotables [1 of 2], 1998 -- 2001; MS014.001.051.00009; Media Research Center (Box 51)
  - Notable Quotables [2 of 2], 1994 -- 2001; MS014.001.051.00010; Media Research Center (Box 51)
  - NRB, 2000; MS014.001.051.00011; National Religious Broadcasters (Box 51)
  - NS Bulletin, 1985 -- 1987; MS014.001.051.00012; New Order (Box 51)
  - NSA Magazine, 1973 -- 1975; MS014.001.051.00013; US National Student Association (Box 51)
  - NSV Report, 1985 -- 1995; MS014.001.051.00014; National Socialist Vanguard (Box 51)
  - Nuestra Lucha, 1981; MS014.001.051.00015; Farm Labor Organizing Committee (Box 51)
  - Nutshell, 1976; MS014.001.051.00016; Approach 13-30 Corporation (Box 51)
  - The Observer of Boston College, 1990; MS014.001.051.00017; Boston College (Box 51)
  - Occasional Papers of the Conservative Citizens' Foundation, 2004; MS014.001.051.00018; Conservative Citizens' Foundation (Box 51)
  - The Odinist, 1989; MS014.001.051.00019 (Box 51)
  - Old Mill News, 1981; MS014.001.051.00020; Society for the Preservation of Old Mills (Box 51)
  - Old News, 1997; MS014.001.051.00021; Susquehanna Times & Magazine (Box 51)
  - Omen of the Future?: The Abortion Pill RU-486, 1986; MS014.001.051.00022; National Right to Life (Box 51)
  - On Campus, 2004 -- 2008; MS014.001.051.00023; Committee for Accuracy in Middle East Reporting in America (Box 51)
  - On Our Way, 2003 -- 2004; MS014.001.051.00024; The Women's Center (Box 51)
  - On Principle [1 of 2], 1982 -- 1983; MS014.001.051.00025; Apriori Publishing (Box 51)
  - On Principle [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1984; MS014.001.051.00026; Apriori Publishing (Box 51)
  - On Target, 1982; MS014.001.051.00027; The Minutemen Organization (Box 51)
  - On Wheels (African Americans), 1999; MS014.001.051.00028; African Americans On Wheels (Box 51)
  - One Country, 2003 -- 2009; MS014.001.051.00029; Baha'I Interntional Community (Box 51)
  - Open Hands, 1993 -- 1994; MS014.001.051.00030; Reconciling Congregation Program (Box 51)
  - Open Issue, 1982; MS014.001.051.00031; United Families Foundation (Box 51)
  - Open Road, 1988; MS014.001.051.00032 (Box 51)
  - Open Secrets, 1995; MS014.001.051.00033; Coalition of Political Assassinations (Box 51)
  - Opposition Notes, 2008; MS014.001.051.00034; Catholics for Choice (Box 51)
  - The Options Handbook, 1976; MS014.001.051.00035; National Student Educational Fund (Box 51)
  - The Oregon Alliance [1 of 2], 1999 -- 2003; MS014.001.051.00036; Oregon Citizens Alliance (Box 51)
  - The Oregon Alliance [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1999; MS014.001.051.00037; Oregon Citizens Alliance (Box 51)
  - Oregon Witness, 1991; MS014.001.051.00038; Coalition for Human Dignity (Box 51)
  - The Organizer, 1982; MS014.001.051.00039; National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression (Box 51)
  - Organizing Notes [1 of 3], 1981 -- 1984; MS014.001.051.00040; Campaign for Political Rights (Box 51)
  - Organizing Notes [2 of 3], 1979 -- 1981; MS014.001.051.00041; Campaign for Political Rights (Box 51)
  - Organizing Notes [3 of 3], 1977 -- 1979; MS014.001.051.00042; Campaign for Political Rights (Box 51)
  - Otto Scott's Compass, 1995; MS014.001.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - Our Lady of Guadalupe Seminary, 1996; MS014.001.052.00002; The Priestly Fraternity of St. Peter (Box 52)
  - Our Right to Know, 1982 -- 1989; MS014.001.052.00003; Fund for Open Information and Accountability, Inc. (Box 52)
  - Our Sunday Visitor, 2008 -- 2009; MS014.001.052.00004 (Box 52)
  - Our Times, 1995; MS014.001.052.00005 (Box 52)
  - Our Voices, 2003 -- 2009; MS014.001.052.00006; Boston Women's Fund (Box 52)
  - Ourselves, 1990 -- 1992; MS014.001.052.00007; Minnesota Chippewa Tribe (Box 52)
  - Out and Out Right News, 1996; MS014.001.052.00008 (Box 52)
  - Out Traveler, 2008; MS014.001.052.00009 (Box 52)
  - Outcome-Based Education, 1994; MS014.001.052.00010; Concerned Women for America (Box 52)
  - Outcry, 1994; MS014.001.052.00011; WELS Lutherans for Life (Box 52)
  - Outline Bible Study, MS014.001.052.00012; Aggressive Christianity Missions Training Corps (Box 52)
  - Outlines, 1994; MS014.001.052.00013 (Box 52)
  - Outlines, 1994; MS014.001.052.00014 (Box 52)
  - Outlook, 2009; MS014.001.052.00015; Asian American Legal Defense and Edcucation Fund (Box 52)
  - Outlook: National Lesbian and Gay Quarterly, 1988; MS014.001.052.00016 (Box 52)
  - Outpost, 1990 -- 1992; MS014.001.052.00017; Americans for a Safe Israel (Box 52)
  - Outpost, 1993 -- 1998; MS014.001.052.00018; Americans for a Safe Israel (Box 52)
  - Outpost, 1999 -- 2004; MS014.001.052.00019; Americans for a Safe Israel (Box 52)
  - Outpost News, 1996 -- 1997; MS014.001.052.00020; Outpost, Inc. (Box 52)
  - Outspoken, 1996 -- 2003; MS014.001.052.00021; International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission (Box 52)
  - Overthrow, 1979 -- 1988; MS014.001.052.00022 (Box 52)
  - Pacific Security Report, 1991; MS014.001.052.00023; Institute for Global Security Studies (Box 52)
  - Pan American Headlines, 1976 -- 1982; MS014.001.052.00024; Committee on Pan American Policy (Box 52)
  - Pan-American Indian Association News, MS014.001.052.00025 (Box 52)
  - Paradigm 2000, 1994 -- 1997; MS014.001.052.00026 (Box 52)
  - Paranoia, 1993; MS014.001.052.00027 (Box 52)
  - Parental Guidance, 1995; MS014.001.052.00028; Focus on the Family (Box 52)
  - Parents and Friends Press, 1999 -- 2000; MS014.001.052.00029; Parents and Friends Ministries (Box 52)
  - Parents Advisory Center News, 1985; MS014.001.052.00030; Eagle Forum (Box 52)
  - Parents Choice, 1992; MS014.001.052.00031; Citizens for Educational Freedom (Box 52)
  - Parents in Education, 1991; MS014.001.052.00032; American Parents Association (Box 52)
  - PARR Issue, 1987 -- 1991; MS014.001.052.00033; Protect American's Rights and Issues (Box 52)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1988; MS014.001.052.00034 (Box 52)
  - The Pastor's Weekly Briefing, 1997 -- 1998; MS014.001.052.00035; Focus on the Family (Box 52)
  - Pat Robertson's Perspective, 1991; MS014.001.052.00036 (Box 52)
  - The Pathfinder, 1988 -- 1991; MS014.001.052.00037; Christ's Gospel Fellowship (Box 52)
  - The Pathfinder, 1990 -- 1994; MS014.001.052.00038; Christ's Gospel Fellowship (Box 52)
  - Pathways, 1996; MS014.001.052.00039; metaphysicsmall.com (Box 52)
  - Pathways, 2008 -- 2010; MS014.001.052.00040 (Box 52)
  - The Patriot Review, 1986 -- 1990; MS014.001.052.00041; CPA Defending the Public (Box 52)
  - Patrick J. Buchanan From the Right, 1989 -- 1991; MS014.001.052.00042 (Box 52)
  - The Patterson Strategy Letter, 1983; MS014.001.052.00043 (Box 52)
  - Peace and Democracy, 1994 -- 1995; MS014.001.052.00044; The Campaign for Peace and Democracy (Box 52)
  - Peace Conversion Times, 1996; MS014.001.052.00045; The Alliance for Survival (Box 52)
  - Peace Developments, 2005 -- 2008; MS014.001.052.00046; Peace Development Fund (Box 52)
  - Peace Through Strength Report, 1984 -- 1987; MS014.001.052.00047; United States Congressional Advisory Board (Box 52)
  - Peacework, 1989 -- 1991; MS014.001.052.00048; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 52)
  - Peacework, 1992 -- 1993; MS014.001.052.00049; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 52)
  - Peacework, 1994 -- 1995; MS014.001.052.00050; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 52)
  - Peacework, 1996 -- 1997; MS014.001.053.00001; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 53)
  - Peacework, 1998; MS014.001.053.00002; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 53)
  - Peacework, 1999 -- 2001; MS014.001.053.00003; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 53)
  - Peacework, 2001 -- 2002; MS014.001.053.00004; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 53)
  - Peacework, 2002 -- 2003; MS014.001.053.00005; New England Peace and Social Justice Newsletter (Box 53)
  - The Pearl, 2004; MS014.001.053.00006; The Embassy of the State of Qatar (Box 53)
  - Peninsula, 1991 -- 1993; MS014.001.053.00007; Peninsula of Harvard (Box 53)
  - Peninsula, 1993 -- 1997; MS014.001.053.00008; Peninsula of Harvard (Box 53)
  - Penn Notes, 2004 -- 2009; MS014.001.053.00009; William Penn House (Box 53)
  - Pennsylvania Families and Schools, 1996 -- 2000; MS014.001.053.00010; Pennsylvania Family Institute (Box 53)
  - People Concerned for the Unborn Child Newsletter, 1982; MS014.001.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - People for the American Way Newsletter, 1983 -- 2003; MS014.001.053.00012; People for the American Way (Box 53)
  - The People, 1999; MS014.001.053.00013; Socialist Labor Party (Box 53)
  - The People's Mouthpiece, 1994; MS014.001.053.00014; Apostolic Overcoming Holy Church of God (Box 53)
  - A People's Story, 1974; MS014.001.053.00015 (Box 53)
  - People's Weekly World, 2001 -- 2003; MS014.001.053.00016 (Box 53)
  - PERC Policy Series, 2003; MS014.001.053.00017; Property and Environment Research Center (Box 53)
  - PERC Reports, 1998 -- 2000; MS014.001.053.00018; Property and Environment Research Center (Box 53)
  - PERC Reports, 2001 -- 2004; MS014.001.053.00019; Property and Environment Research Center (Box 53)
  - PERC Reports, 2001 -- 2008; MS014.001.053.00020; Property and Environment Research Center (Box 53)
  - PERC Reports, 2008 -- 2011; MS014.001.053.00021; Property and Environment Research Center (Box 53)
  - Perceptions Magazine, 1995; MS014.001.053.00022 (Box 53)
  - Perhaps Today, 2001; MS014.001.053.00023; Jack Van Impe Ministries (Box 53)
  - Perspectives, 1994; MS014.001.053.00024; Toward Tradition (Box 53)
  - Perspectives, 1982; MS014.001.053.00025; US Comission on Civil Rights (Box 53)
  - Perspectives, 2001; MS014.001.053.00026; The Prejudice Institute (Box 53)
  - Persuasion at Work, 1981 -- 1985; MS014.001.053.00027; The Rockford Institute (Box 53)
  - Phoenix Journal Express, 1991; MS014.001.053.00028 (Box 53)
  - The Peoenix Liberator, 1992; MS014.001.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - The Phyllis Schlafly Report, 1981 -- 1987; MS014.001.054.00001; The Eagle Trust Fund (Box 54)
  - The Phyllis Schlafly Report, 1987 -- 1991; MS014.001.054.00002; The Eagle Trust Fund (Box 54)
  - The Phyllis Schlafly Report, 1992 -- 1996; MS014.001.054.00003; The Eagle Trust Fund (Box 54)
  - The Phyllis Schlafly Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS014.001.054.00004; The Eagle Trust Fund (Box 54)
  - The Phyllis Schlafly Report, 1999 -- 2004; MS014.001.054.00005; The Eagle Trust Fund (Box 54)
  - Physician, 1993 -- 1999; MS014.001.054.00006; Focus on the Family (Box 54)
  - PIC Newsletter, 1994; MS014.001.054.00007; National Writers Union (Box 54)
  - The Pilgrim Way, 1999; MS014.001.054.00008 (Box 54)
  - The Pilot [1 of 15], 1994; MS014.001.054.00009; Boston's Catholic Newspaper (Box 54)
  - The Pilot [2 of 15], 1994; MS014.001.054.00010; Boston's Catholic Newspaper (Box 54)
  - The Pilot [3 of 15], 1995; MS014.001.054.00011; Boston's Catholic Newspaper (Box 54)
  - The Pilot [4 of 15], 1995; MS014.001.054.00012; Boston's Catholic Newspaper (Box 54)
  - The Pilot [5 of 15], 1996; MS014.001.054.00013; Boston's Catholic Newspaper (Box 54)
  - The Pilot [6 of 15], 1996; MS014.001.055.00001; Boston's Catholic Newspaper (Box 55)
  - The Pilot [7 of 15], 1996; MS014.001.055.00002; Boston's Catholic Newspaper (Box 55)